I look up to the stars and reach for
the sky I believe in tomorrow if we try!
Hey!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music!
We share the music!
Come on, let's go, baby, baby!
Oh, we share the one dream!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the good times!
We share the good times!
Let's go, baby, baby,
always share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see or to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought on by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try high.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Come on let's go everybody.
Oh we share the music.
Come on let's go baby baby.
Oh we share the one world.
Oh as we chase we're being chased.
From the top we go on straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know that you are there.
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me.
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go.
Beyond far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go.
Maybe, maybe.
Oh, we share the one world.
Heavens, my heart is a flutter.
I feel I might do
anything Luffy asks of me.
I acquiesce without a second thought.
And I don't regret it,
not even the slightest.
That's what they call love. Love?
Once it has a hold on your heart.
It will squeeze and squeeze.
Until you fall over dead.
If you cannot be with the one you desire?
The empresses that came before
you all fell in love with men as
well but as They were unable to
leave their kingdom they were forced
to bottle up their Feelings while
they stayed their heartache grew
and grew until the pain Was so
great that they died from sorrow.
Little did you know that by
agreeing to his request you may have
saved your Own life although you
were struck with love sickness
if Luffy had not arrived And
requested this very thing you would
have lost your title as warlord
and led this kingdom to ruin.
However one may say that
he is just as fortunate
as you after all had fate
not brought him to this
Island the only way he
could hope to enter that
prison would be in chains
just like his brother.
I thought he wasn't leaving the kingdom
until tomorrow though I
heard there was a last
minute Change of plans now he's getting on
a navy ship along with a snake princess.
Hi Luffy.
Hey guys.
Thanks for everything.
This was fun.
I'll come back to visit and
bring my friends next time.
They're all guys except Nami and Robin
but it's no fun if we can't all visit.
Even if men are forbidden here I
think they'll make an exception.
The snake princess seems
to favor you so it's
not likely that they would
be sentenced to death.
Well probably not at least.
And there's our empress now.
Who had the audacity to place
these beasts in my path?
Detestable.
Peacefully adorable obstacles.
We love you, princess!
If I was half the sexiest, sir, I'd
spend all day in front of a mirror.
She's even more striking than usual.
I didn't think that was possible.
My deepest apologies.
I accept full responsibility.
You should be more careful.
Hey, looks like you're feeling all better.
Hate to be rude but we
gotta hurry snake lady
I can't look him in the eye it's too much.
That's rude Luffy you can't call her snake
lady it's snake princess don't forget it.
You can simply call me
hancock if you like.
Cool whatever works for
you hammock it's a hancock.
The snake princess just smiled at me!
It's like a diamond snow!
It's like the stars in the sky!
I'm dazzled!
The spark of a woman in love!
It makes me long for the
sweet days of my youth!
Is something wrong, Granny Young?
Your face is looking rather grotesque!
I'll kill you!
Have a safe trip, snake princess!
We'll miss you, Luffy!
Come back soon!
Bye-bye!
Would you stop that?
Can you guarantee that you'll
honor the promise you made earlier?
I contacted my superiors.
As long as we're quick about
it, we can stop by Impel Down.
To be clear only you
and your snake may board
unless they're shackled
pirates are not welcome.
At the prison they'll watch you like a hawk
whatever you do please try to stay safe.
Strike down all who oppose
you sister good luck
in the battle with white
beard snake princess.
Luffy i hope you i shall return
soon guard the kingdom in my absence
of course i'm glad i stuck around
i feared i might have to return
to headquarters of failure it would
be shameful to show up at navy
headquarters in this unsightly state
they are alive aren't they awaken
huh what happened get ready for
departure yes sir right away
We'll make a stop at Impel Down
before we return to Marineford
Fleet Admiral Sengoku we have
word from Vice Admiral Momonga
Snake Princess Boa
Hancock came to speak with
them again She finally
agreed to our conditions
I'm told that they're
on their way now It's
about time Let's just
hope they're not late?
That woman is quite formidable.
Now we'll have six of the
seven warlords with us.
And the seventh?
Did a little time in prison cool his head?
Perhaps he's ready to
aid in our fight now.
No, sir.
Just as before, he's
adamantly refusing to fight.
He went so far as to say he would
relinquish his title as warlord.
Given his disposition,
I had assumed that he would be
the most cooperative of the bunch.
This is not the time to
get hung up on principle.
We need you, Team Bay.
Fleet Admiral, sir!
I have an announcement.
We have a small issue with the 500 pirates
that Admiral Kizaru captured at Sabaody.
That is to say, the staff had
impelled down so they can't hold them.
Send them to a labor camp.
Frankly, if it doesn't
have to do with Whitebeard,
I just don't have time for it right now.
I understand, sir, but St.
Roswald is...
Let the admirals handle it for once.
And where the hell is Garp?
I already informed you, sir, but he
left for Impel Down quite some time ago.
I guess I should expect that kind
of behavior from that old bastard,
but not before a battle.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm afraid we have a situation.
Whitebeard's ship is advancing.
I see.
I assume the guard ships are on the line?
Put me through.
I'd rather speak to them directly.
I can't do that. Huh?
We lost contact, sir,
with all 23 Navy vessels keeping tabs on
Whitebeard's main ship, the Moby Dick.
Given the circumstances, we can only
conclude they were eliminated by the enemy.
Surely not the whole fleet.
There's been some worrying activity from
other pirate ships in
the New World as well.
Without guard ships,
we won't have any idea how many ships the
enemy is sending or
when he's sending them.
I've arranged for replacements,
but we're in the dark right now.
We've been had.
I didn't think they would act so quickly.
Until new ships are in
place, we're flying blind.
As long as Ace is there, they may even
have the audacity to strike Impel down.
So be ready for anything! Yes, sir!
Vice Admiral, it will be right this way.
Please, be careful.
Sure.
You're right, mess boy.
I hate to see it.
You still breathing in there?
Yes.
Not long ago, only a few
days before, in fact?
Be careful now!
young lady young lady who came
Plummeting out of the sky!
Yeah, I heard you what?
Do you think you've
calmed down a little now?
No more inclinations toward violence!
Yeah.
This may look like ordinary rope.
But they are in fact
tightly wound wind knots.
If I untie one, It
creates a gentle breeze.
But if I untie two, A
strong gust will blow.
And if I untie three, It becomes a gale.
What'd you do that for?
I'm sorry, I just thought it
might cheer you up, that's all.
Oh, yeah, I'm real cheery now.
This is a small sky
island called Weatheria.
We conduct studies of
the weather here. What?
This is a sky island?
And so Nami found herself on
a small island in the sky.
Will she ever be able to find
her way back to her friends?
Huh?
Hold on, wait!
What are you doing?
Come on!
Huh?
No, stop!
What?
He's a human?
This is terrible.
What are we gonna do?
Um, excuse me, are you all right, sir?
My dog, he thought you were
something we're hunting.
Yeah, no biggie. Ah!
It's like this guy doesn't even care!
There is one problem, though.
Where the heck am I,
and how did I get here?
It's cold. Damn.
Don't you have the sun here?
Franky!
Oh, no.
He's only wearing
underwear in all the snow.
Did bandits steal your pants?
Why don't you put on this fur pelt?
Oh, a fur pelt? No, thanks.
I'm trying to maintain a style here.
That'd cramp my reputation.
As a freak!
Oh, I gotta move, man!
Like this. Wow.
Come on. Follow my lead.
Shake your hips to the right.
Right hand to the waist.
And then stick out your left hand.
Now slide and reverse.
Now repeat after me, guys!
One, two, one, two, right,
left, right, left, top!
Super!
That's how it's done!
Crap!
I'm still freezing!
Where the hell is this place?
What?
You don't know where you are?
Why would I know something like that?
This is the Futureland Baltimore,
which is located on Mechanical Island.
Behold, Peachy Island, a dreamy,
beautiful destination on the Grand Line.
Everything here is pink.
All of the animals and people who
come to this land share a common bond.
No matter what forms their bodies
take, they still have girlish hearts.
I thought it, I think this was heaven!
Leave me alone, you weirdos!
As I already told you, I'm
not into that kind of crap!
My dearest Nami, my sweet
Robin, it's been a while.
How are the two of you doing?
As for me, I'm, well, uh, how to put this?
Welcome to Kamabaka Kingdom!
No, it's obvious.
I'm in hell.
Like a flower blossoming
in the middle of the ocean,
we now arrive at the Bowen Islands.
How are ya?
You're rather energetic today!
gonna eat that are you kidding but
you saved my life so you can eat
whatever you want thank you whoever you
are my name is heracleson wow that's
a pretty cool name you got there
really think so i'm Usopp nice to meet
you oh is this thing edible i've
never seen this kind of fruit before
Sure, Usoppun. It's fine.
By the way, you can call me Periclesan!
Yeah, okay.
Heard you the first time.
Well, it definitely smells
delicious, at least.
Maybe I'll just give it a little lick.
Usoppun!
What the?
Was that thing a plant?
And did it really just try to eat me?
Sure, they are man-eating
Glanston. Man-eating?
What the hell is this place?
This is the Swindling Forest,
Glanston. Help! Help! Help!
Is is this the devil?
Look, our magic incantation
actually worked!
What a dreadful looking creature.
No kidding!
It's not of this world!
This is what we've waited for!
Our prayers are answered!
We'll have our revenge at last!
We don't have anything left!
The long arm tribe took everything!
The Bastards laid claim to
everything we hold dear.
Oh great and powerful Satan Please
grant us our wish in exchange.
We are prepared to offer
our souls up to you
Leave them bloody and begging for death
What is this place how far have I been
carried away from all of my two friends?
Whatever their plight I must aid them.
I'll return to meet the
others at once. Wait!
Just a moment.
Please don't go back to
hell yet, Master Satan.
Quickly, men!
We've got to stop him.
We need to.
Offer him more.
What could we possibly
offer, Master Satan?
A sacrifice.
What do I want?
Paul.
Pardon me.
Would you be so kind as
to show me your panties?
He wants to see your underwear!
Everyone show him your underwear!
Tequila Wolf is a nation of laborers.
Paul! Paul!
The people we have constantly
toiling away to build
this bridge are criminals
from all over the world.
Either that or they're
citizens of countries
that refuse to ally with
the world government.
On your feet!
In short, they're slaves.
How much longer until
the bridge is complete?
I have no idea, but it's been under
constant construction for 700 years now.
700?
But for what purpose?
You don't need to concern
yourself with that.
Now that you're here,
we're putting you to work,
so the only thing you need to
worry about is making the bridge.
Got it?
Hey, where the heck did
these birds go from?
They're huge!
Don't even think about trying to eat me!
No!
My body's too stiff to get up and run!
I gotta move!
No! Stop it!
Leave me alone!
It's over now, I think.
Rare to get raccoon on an island.
Raccoon hotpot! Stop it! Shut up!
I'm a reindeer!
Ah, guess we have reindeer hotpot then.
Hey, wait, did reindeer
just say something?
This island is known as Birdie Kingdom,
a place where birds reign supreme.
One legend suggests that its lands
are filled with hidden treasure,
but all Chopper has found his danger.
Look, I know what I said.
If I were to travel anywhere in the world,
I would want to go someplace dark
and damp with a creepy old castle.
and I would spend all my days
singing songs of curses, but,
stupid Kuma,
I didn't know the castle wouldn't have
any maids, no servants, nothing cute,
no bagel sandwiches and hot chocolate
served to be in bed every morning,
and to top it off there isn't
a single stuffed animal here,
where in the heck am I,
oh Kuma C, I miss you, I want to
go back to Thriller Park again,
What was that?
Yes, I knew it!
Someone else was exiled here just like me!
Oh, I hope it's someone cute!
No.
Is that...
It is!
It's one of the Straw Hats!
Kuma must have beaten him
and launched him here.
Also, he looks pretty dead?
I'm alive.
But where am I?
Where am I and why are you here?
I could ask you the same thing.
Also, don't scream like that.
What did you do with my swords?
Oh, you won't be getting those back.
I'm warning you.
Ha!
You're not so tough.
Or rather, I'm just super awesome.
And now we return to the present, where
Luffy is steadily speeding over the waves?
to the great prison Impel Down
to rescue his brother Ace.
How many times must I repeat myself?
Are my instructions too complicated
to penetrate that thick head of yours?
I require at least 100
kilos of food per meal.
Anything less than that is
completely insufficient.
Do you want to be turned to stone again?
No, please.
We're very sorry.
We'll be more careful next time.
Bring her another meal to her
specifications to replace this one.
Whoa, look at that.
It's a warning.
If anyone ever tries to peek into
a room, this is what will happen.
She's so scary.
Here you are, Luffy.
Open wide for me, okay?
Simply delectable.
And when you're the one feeding it to me?
Why, it makes it all the sweeter.
Oh, go on.
Clearly, that's exactly what he would say.
What are you doing over there?
Who are you talking to?
Aren't you going to eat something?
This Sea King has unbelievable.
No, no, it's fine.
Please, help yourself.
I'm more than satisfied, just as I am.
can't eat another bite that was so good
quiet don't forget
you're a stowaway if you
don't keep it down you'll be found excuse
me is someone else in
your room with you oh
damn it lieutenant stalker are you certain
about this yes sir i
just heard someone say
oh i couldn't eat
another bite and i hardly
think that the empress
would say that to you
He's right she'd never say that and if she
did I'll give myself a mohawk same here
Um I couldn't eat another bite
There I'm finished for
now take these plates away
Oh, yes, and don't forget, I require
the same amount five times every day.
That's a lot!
But if we give you that much,
how are we supposed to eat?
Frankly, I don't care if
you all starve to death.
That's awful!
But whatever, she's hot!
There are now only six days left until
the public execution of Portgas V. Ace.
With their guard ships destroyed
at the hands of Whitebeard,
Tensions at Navy Headquarters are rising.
Famous Marines from all over the world
are gathering at the harbor of Marineford,
prepared to battle to
the death, if need be.
In the name of justice,
they ready their swords,
not for any mere battle, but for war.
Meanwhile, in the holy land of Marijwa,
the seven warlords are
summoned for a meeting?
to determine their roles in the
event that Whitebeard attacks.
Profumes that they are, however, they
have little taste for the discussion.
The mood in the room is tense,
and all hopes for teamwork
or any sort of organization?
are quickly put to rest.
Because of you, Navy Headquarters is...
No, all of the world government is a mess.
Just kill me.
Do it.
Kill me now.
So you want to die, huh?
You damned fool.
Nothing can be done now.
Everything's in motion.
Even if you were to die right now, that
won't stop Whitebeard from fighting.
There's nothing that can
stop that anymore, son.
Seems the Navy has made
the king of the sea.
Mad as hell.
What is this?